[{"answer": "Wha", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I was bowlin", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "So you have no frame of reference, my friend.  You're like a child who wanders in in the middle of a movie and wants to kno", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "There's no fucking reaso", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "That is indeed Mr. my friend with the first lady, yes, taken whe", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Of course, Mr. my friend on the right, Mrs.  my friend on the left, taken whe", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend's pretty good", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Are these", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Wonderful woman.  We were ver", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "These are Mr. my friend's children, so to spea", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "So you know they were trying to piss on your ru", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You mean, did you personally come and pee on m", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Huh.  I did not know that.  Well, it's water under the bridge.  And we do enter the next roun", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Am I wrong", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "My point, my friend, is why should we settle for twenty grand when we can keep the entire million.  Am I wrong", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It is a fucking game.  You said so yourself, my frien", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Huh?  The problem i", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, my friend!  I said I thought she kidnapped herself!  You're the one who's so fucking certai", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well that's just, that's the stress talking, Dude.  So far we have what looks to me like a series of victimless crime", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "FORGET ABOUT THE FUCKING TOE", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You think veer kidding und making mit de funny stuff", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Ja, vee could really do it, my friend. Vee belief in nossing", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh for Chris", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Now that is ridiculous, Dude.  No one is going to cut your dick off", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "From who", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, no, not exactly.  It's a complicated case, my friend.  Lotta ins. Lotta outs.  And a lotta strands to keep in my head, man.  Lotta strands in old my friend'", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Huh?  No, really, I don't even have the bruise any more, ", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I thought you might know, man", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "But she hasn't run off, she's bee", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Finder's fee", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It's not my father's money, it's the Foundation's.  Why did he think you had it?  And who does", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No no, the wealth was all Mother's", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "We did let Father run one of the companies, briefly, but he didn't do very well at it", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I understand.  That's why I picked up the phone", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Dude, I'm not supposed to make call", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm not ", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "She's not my special lady, she's my fucking lady friend.  I'm just helping her conceive, man", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Hey hey, I'm not messing with your special lad", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Hey, man, I'm no", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "It's all over, man!  We call your fucking bluff", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Sure, I'll put him down, Dude.  RAUSS! ACHTUNG, BABY!", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes, so we were informed.  However, we must of course transmit the remains to you in a receptacle", "docId": "Big-Lebowski_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yes sir.  It is our most modestly priced receptacle", "qsentId": 44}]